winhost.com 2018-09-08

# Winhost Privacy Policy | Winhost ASP.NET Hosting

Winhost is committed to protecting each customer's privacy. This Privacy Policy sets forth our privacy practices with regard to the information that we collect when you interact with our website and services. By accessing Winhost's website and services, you consent to the information collection and use described within. The use of any information collected is only used for the purpose of providing Winhost services. 

#### Personal Information

Users can purchase Winhost services by completing our online order form and through order forms within the Winhost control panel. As part of the order form, we will request personal contact information and financial information. Any contact information is used to contact the customer to provide our services and inform you of any new services or information that we think will be of interest to you. Financial information is used only to bill for the Winhost services purchased.

#### Data Supplementation

We may receive additional information from third party sources, including publicly available databases, and combine this data with your account records. 

#### Secure Forms

When collecting personally identifiable information, we use forms protected by industry standard secure sockets layer (SSL) technology. Using SSL protected forms, all personally identifiable information is encrypted during data transport.

#### Data Retention

We will retain your information as long as your account is active and as needed to provide services to you, and as necessary to comply with legal obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce our agreements. 

#### Third Party Vendors

To provide you services, we use third party services. For example, credit card processing companies to fulfill transactions, a email service provider to manage email lists and send bulk email, a domain registrar partner to register your domain names. As required by some partners and services, such as domain name registration, we must share your contact information so that the third party can provide the service. 

Third party vendor services that are included or used as part of the Winhost services have their own privacy policies and you acknowledge that Winhost has no control over third party policies and is not responsible for their privacy practices. We will provide you with links to Third Party Vendor websites upon your written request. 

#### Single Sign-on

For improved user experience in using some third party services, we may provide single sign-on capabilities from the Winhost control panel. These services authenticate your identity and provide you access to a third party portal without having to enter login credentials each time you access their portal. 

#### Information Disclosure

Winhost will not disclose or share personally identifiable information with third parties without your permission except when necessary to provide resolution to a service request, to comply with federal or state law or subpoenas, or to comply with liquidation or mergers and acquisition-related activities.

#### Aggregate Statistics

Winhost may use aggregate statistical information to modify our services or improve the usability of our website. We do not use this data to identify you individually. Winhost may share aggregate statistical information regarding its customers, including survey results, with partners or other third parties. In no way, will this information be personally identifiable.

#### Cookies, Website Stats, Image Markers and other Tracking Software

Winhost uses cookies, website traffic statistics, image markers, visitor IP address, and other tracking software to help improve our website, services, and marketing effectiveness. For example, we use cookies to analyze repeat visits to our website, we use website statistics to analyze how visitors use and interact with our website and other web properties, we use image markers in email campaigns to understand how many users opened a particular email message, and we use other tracking tools to measure advertising effectiveness.

Users have control over the use of cookies within their web browsers. However, if you reject cookies, your ability to use some features of our site may be limited.

#### Third Party Advertisers

Winhost uses third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Website. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address, or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, [click here](http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp).

#### Google Adwords

Winhost uses Google Adwords to advertise this site. When you view or click on an ad, cookies are used to help provide better targeted advertisements that may be of interest to you on other Websites. You may opt-out of the use of these cookies through the [Google Advertising and Privacy page](https://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html).

#### Opt-out

Winhost provides an opt-out option for customers who purchase a product or service from Winhost to unsubscribe from news, announcements and marketing material that we may send to customers from time to time. An unsubscribe link is located at the bottom of all announcement and marketing emails that we send out. If a customer no longer wishes to receive Winhost newsletters, news, announcements, and promotional email, they may opt-out of receiving them by following the instructions included in such emails and opting out through their control panel.

#### Accessing and Updating Personally Identifiable Information

If you want to view or update your Personally Identifiable Information, you can do so through the Winhost Control Panel located at [https://cp.winhost.com](https://cp.winhost.com/). If you cannot log into your control panel, you may contact us at support@winhost.com and we will assist you. We will respond to your request within a reasonable timeframe. For privacy and security, we may take steps to verify your identity before updates or removal of information. 

If you cancel your account, any information that was public prior to cancellation may remain stored on our servers and may remain remain accessible to the public.

You may request the deletion or restriction of processing of your personal information. However, Winhost may not be able to provide all or some of our services, should such personal information be deleted or its use restricted.

If you wish to file a complaint about any of our information collection and use, you can email us at support@winhost.com and/or you can also contact a local data protection authority. 

#### Forums and Blog

Winhost maintains a forum and blog. If you choose to use our forum or blog, please be aware that any personally identifiable information you submit there is public and can be read, collected by other users of the forums and blog and could potentially be used to send you unsolicited messages. Winhost is not responsible for the personally identifiable information you choose to submit. You may request the removal of your personally identifiable information from our forum or blog at support@winhost.com and we will do our best effort to remove the content. 

As part of the forum, there is a publicly accessible member directory. If you wish to be removed from the directory, contact support@winhost.com.

#### Business Transition

If Winhost has a business transition, such as a merger or acquisition, or a partial asset sale, it is possible that your personally identifiable information may be part of the assets transferred. You will be notified by email of any such change in ownership or control of your personally identifiable information.

#### Policy Changes

Winhost may update this privacy policy in its sole discretion. When updated, we will revise the "last updated" date at the bottom of this page. Your continued use of the website and service constitutes your agreement to this privacy policy and any updates. We will notify you via email when material changes are made to this privacy policy.

If you have questions regarding our Privacy Policy or its implementation, please send an email to [sales@winhost.com](mailto:sales@winhost.com) and our Sales team will route your inquiry to the appropriate staff member.

#### Contact Information

Winhost  
80 W. Sierra Madre Blvd. #272  
Sierra Madre, CA 91024  

Last updated May 21st, 2018.
